fusioncash.net 2018-10-10

# FusionCash

We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.   
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically logs information regarding the domain and/or IP address, time of access, referring site, and content accessed. The information we collect is: 

  * used to improve the content of our site,
  * used internally for marketing purposes,
  * used to prevent and respond to hacking and other illicit activities, and
  * never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes except under your explicit direction.

This site uses cookies. ([What's a cookie?](http://www.netlingo.com/word/cookies.php))  
In order to fully utilize this website, users are required to complete our registration form. 

During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information, except in the case that you select "Yes" to opt-in to an offer displayed on our site. It is gathered only to contact the user about services on our site for which he or she has expressed interest and shared only with your consent. 

Registration is not required to access this site; however, most features require registration. 

We require additional information from the user in order to disburse payment. A user must provide information such as name, email, and/or mailing address in order to receive payment. 

When completing some offers, some or all of your contact information may be "pre-populated" on the advertiser's site. This industry-standard practice is intended to make the offer completion process easier. **Your contact information is not collected by the advertiser unless you "submit" the form.**

If you "opt-in" to an advertiser offer that has a "Yes/No" radio button next to it, FusionCash automatically transmits one or more of: email address, name, street address, and/or demographic information to the advertiser(s) you selected. 

Certain features of FusionCash, provided by third parties, require that we transmit one or more of: email address, name, street address, and/or demographic information. These parties are contractually obligated to protect your data and use it only in conjunction with providing services on FusionCash. Further details can be found in Section VIII. of the Terms of Service. 

Upon visiting the "FC Surveys" page, one or more cookies may be placed for the purpose of offering you surveys related to ads on other websites. 

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, members who are California residents can request certain information about our transmittal of personal information to third parties. If you would like to make an information request and you are a California resident, please send an email to [support@fusioncash.net](mailto:support@fusioncash.net) or write to us:  
    FUSIONCASH, INC.  
    PO BOX 7095  
    SANTA CRUZ, CA 95061-7095

FusionCash may share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number ("UID"), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a "Third Party MR Company" and collectively the "Third Party MR Companies") for the following purposes: 

  1. Identifying client survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies; and
  2. isclosing such data elements to clients of the Third Party MR Companies for audience measurement services; and
  3. Appending such data elements to completed client surveys and delivering the appended survey data to clients of the Third Party MR Company(ies) for analytical or research purposes.

If you are eligible for a client survey opportunity offered through a Third Party MR Company, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the client survey through email invitations and/or posting on the FC Surveys page. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States, and by agreeing to this privacy policy you are agreeing to the processing and exportation of your personal information as set forth in this Section. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact FusionCash or you can opt-out by clicking here. If you opt-out, it is the responsibility of us to inform the Third Party MR Companies. Please note that FusionCash is solely liable and responsible for managing all opt-out requests. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third Party MR Companies. 

FusionCash sends three types of emails: 

  * email confirmation requests (when you sign up initially or change your email address or password)
  * offer completion notifications (when you are credited for completing an offer)
  * occasional newsletters (no more often than twice per calendar month)

You may unsubscribe from newsletters at any time. Once unsubscribed, you will no longer receive the newsletter. 

For security reasons, we do not allow users to unsubscribe from account confirmation or completion notification emails. If you do not wish to receive those emails, simply cease logging in, as they are sent only when triggered by user actions. You are also permitted to deactivate your account, which will prevent you from receiving notification emails.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.
